Finding Aid for Wilson Family Papers
William L. Clements Library, University of Michigan
- Agricultural Society
  - Misc., ca. 1816-ca. 1830 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Anonymous
  - Day Book, 1825-1826 (Box 41, Folder 12)
- Banks and Banking
  - 1814 August 20-1855 [see index for complete list] (Box 41, Folder 13)
- Bridges, Highways and Railroads
  - 1796 October 1-1849 October 22 (Box 41, Folder 14)
- Church Assessments
  - 1818 November 2-1828 December 12 (Box 41, Folder 15)
- Clermont, N.Y.
  - Accounts, [1799]-1803 August 3 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Arrest warrants, 1798 April 18-1800 December 2 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Clermont Academy, 1834 February 4-ca. 1900 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Constable, 1798 April 9-1811 June 18 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Elected Officials, 1795 April 7-1804 January 4 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Misc. local history, 1811 December 1-1901 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Schools, 1796 March 15-1824 August 1 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Tavern licenses, 1795 March 2-1817 March 04 (Box 41, Folder 23)
- Deeds
  - 1714 October 25-1846 June 11 (Box 41, Folder 24)
- Election Returns
  - Columbia County, 1790-1864 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - N.Y. State, 1789-1844 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - U.S., 1787-1840 (Box 41, Folder 27)
- Elections
  - Candidate lists, 1850s-1860s (Box 41, Folder 28)
- Estates
  - B-H (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Cockburn, James, 1798 September-1809 January 16 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Cockburn, James, Account with Wm. Wilson, 1786 May 6-1794 December 11 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Livingston, Robert C. (1742-1794), Leases, 1797 January 1-1807 April 21 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Livingston, Robert C. (1742-1794), Legal papers, accounts, misc., 1790 June 2-1809 July 03 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Livingston, Robert R. (1746-1813), Accounts, 1812 May 1-1827 June 22 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Livingston, Robert R. (1746-1813), Administration, Misc., 1792 November-1825 January 29 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Livingston, Robert R. (1746-1813), Debts owed to/by estate, 1813 May 24-1823 July 22 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Livingston, Robert R. (1746-1813), Leases and sales, 1801 May 1-1827 June 22 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Livingston family, undated (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - N-W (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Wilson, Robert L., 1826 October-1833 May 20 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Wilson, William, 1830 April 23-1855 December 3 (Box 42, Folder 10)
- Genealogy
  - 1868 January 11-ca. 1930, [see index for list of families] (Box 42, Folder 11)
- General Post Office
  - Accounts, 1810-1829 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Accounts, 1830-1849 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Corespondence, Misc., 1815 February 23-1842 January 23; 1935 March 6-9 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Receipts, 1799 January 25-1849 April 1 (Box 42, Folder 15)
- Highland Turnpike Co.
  - Correspondence, Joseph Howland to Wm. Wilson, 1812 June 25-1825 December 29 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Joseph Howland to Wm. H. Wilson, 1826 January 25-1833 June 4 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Misc. and accounts, 1810 May-1829 February 24 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Land Grants
  - 1738 February 7-1813 April 12 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Law--Cases [see index for complete list of litigants]
  - Bank, Franklin v Stephen Gould, 1823 August 29-1826 December 5 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Bartlett, Robert v James Matthews, 1825 December 13-1827 June 4 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Benedict, James v Dudley Shelden et al., 1828 June 20-September 22 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Brown, John C. v George C. Lamb, 1826 June 20-December 7 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Cantello, William J. v Charles Langlois, 1826 December-1827 October 25 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Corbin, Francis P. v Townshend Cock and Joel Conklin, 1828 March 3-April 22 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Corry, Samuel v John I. Webb, 1828 December 3-1829 April 16 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Deming, Lemuel v John M. Willard, 1827 September-1828 March 4 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Hall, Henry v Anthony Kerr, 1828 May 26-1830 May 17 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Hamlin, Asher P. (heirs) v John van Vechten, 1825 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Harrison, William (estate) v Edmund Elmendorph, Stephen Gould, et al., 1823 January 17-1827 March 5 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Hattrick, Peter v Reformed Protestant Dutch Church of the City ofNew York, 1825 June-November 9 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Langlois, Charles v William Canbtello, 1826 January 27-1828 July 18 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Livingston, Robert R. (1746-1813) v Henry Walter, 1799 October 16-22 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Lynch, Dominick v William P. Page, 1827 November 1-1828 May (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Lynch, Henry v Brasher, 1829 April 10 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Lynch, Henry v. Whitehead Howard, 1827 May-1828 May 30 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Misc. accounts and receipts, 1787 June 21-1830 June 21 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Misc. correspondence, 1797 April 20-1829 November 04 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Slocomb, Jared v John E. Ross, 1828 October 1-1829 April 10 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Smith, John P. v Morris Reade, 1827 April 3-1829 October (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Stone, Frederick W. v George C. Lamb, 1826 November 30-1827 February 27 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Thompson, William A. v John L. Norton, 1828 May 22-1830 February 18 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Tice, John v John L. Norton, 1829 March 27-October 30 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Van Ness, Jacob v Henry Lynk, 1799 April 27-December 19 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Van Ness, Jacob v Henry Walter, 1799 April 26-1800 July 2 (Box 43, Folder 30)
- Leases
  - 1742 May 25-1799 December 20 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - 1801 April 15-1863 October 17 (Box 43, Folder 32)
- Lee, John
  - Medical Day Book, 1795 August 14-1796 December 12 (Box 43, Folder 33)
- Legal Actions
  - Bankruptcy, 1800 June 5-1801 September 15 (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - Bonds (notes of indebtedness), 1796 May 4-1825 April 17 (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - Confiscation (property), 1797 August 19-1828 October 23 (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - Contracts, 1815 May-1825 May 14 (Box 43, Folder 37)
  - Deed of Trust, 1816 February 26 (Box 43, Folder 38)
  - Depositions, 1795 May 23-1797 September 27 (Box 43, Folder 39)
  - Ejectment, ca. 1805 (Box 43, Folder 40)
  - Indenture, 1795 September 7-December 10 (Box 43, Folder 41)
  - Misc., 1796 October 8-1829 February 9 (Box 43, Folder 42)
  - Notarized statements, 1816 November 4-1826 May 11 (Box 43, Folder 43)
  - Paternity suits, 1796 October 8-1805 May 9 (Box 43, Folder 44)
  - Power of Attorney, 1793 October-1827 October 11 (Box 43, Folder 45)
  - Subpoenas, 1796 November 4-1803 June 11 (Box 43, Folder 46)
- Leroy, Levi
  - Account Book, 1846-1850 (Box 43, Folder 47)
- Livingston, T. Ferguson
  - Rental account, 1806 (Box 43, Folder 48)
- Merchants' Accounts
  - A (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Bac-Bee (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Bel-Bog (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Bon (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Bos-But (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Cad-Clu (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Coc-Cur (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Dai-Dib (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Dic-Duy (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - E-F (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - G (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Hai-Haw (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Hee-Hof (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Hol-I (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - J-K (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Lam-Lew (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Lit-Lyn (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Mac-Mey (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Mid-Mye (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Misc. (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - N (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - O (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - P (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Rac-Roi (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Roo-Ryk (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Sag-Smi (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Sny-Swo (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - T-U (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Val-VanDyk (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - VanEtt-Vra (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Wac-Whi (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Wig-Wil (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Win-You (Box 45, Folder 16)
- Mortgages
  - 1799 December 14-1829 October 6 (Box 45, Folder 17)
- New York Medical College
  - 1810 September 17 (Box 45, Folder 18)
- New York Medical Society
  - 1811 April 16-1814 January 6 (Box 45, Folder 19)
- Receipts
  - Livingston, 1790-1816 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Misc., 1791-1855 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Wilson, Robert L., 1817-1829 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Wilson, William, 1786-1829 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Wilson, William H., 1819-1857 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Rental Accounts [Lists of tenants with rent owed]
  - Livingston family, 1790 May 17-1807 April 20 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Misc., 1785 March 16-1803 March 7 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Rental, Miscellaneous
  - 1798 May 24-1826 June 21 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Rental Receipts [Individual receipts for rent paid]
  - Livingston family, 1790-1799 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Livingston family, 1800-1856 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Wilson, 1799 January 9-1811 June 7 (Box 46, Folder 7)
- Surveys and Surveying
  - 1741 August 18-1816 July 13 (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Taxation, Clermont; Columbia County, N.Y.; et al.
  - 1787-1873 April 18 (Box 46, Folder 9)
- Wilson, Alicia Ann
  - School exercise book, 1811 July 17-October 13 (Box 46, Folder 10)
- Wilson, Robert L.
  - Account Book, 1821 March 14-1827 June (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Bankbooks, 1816 March 13-1829 October 1 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Checkbooks, 1826 May 4-1830 March 30 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Legal Account Book, 1815 October 31-1821 December 18 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Legal Account Book, 1824 August-1830 March 27 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Legal Notebook, 1814 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Register of legal cases, 1823 May 20-1830 February 22 (Box 46, Folder 17)
- Wilson, William
  - Account Book, 1783 December-1793 January (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Account Book, 1799-1815 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Agricultural Notebook, 1810-1816 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Bank Books, 1809 August 7-1814 May 31 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Checks, 1807 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Daybooks, 1789 September-1792 November; 1799 January 1-1803 November 3 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Diary of passage to N.Y., 1784 April 24-June 20 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Index to account books, ca. 1795 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Index to rent ledger, undated (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Individual medical accounts, 1791 November 1-1799 March 10 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Medical Daybook, 1784 July 8-1797 October 23 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Medical Daybook, 1787 December 4-1790 April 28 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Medical Daybook, 1790 May 1-1792 August 31 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Medical Daybook, 1793 January 20-1794 March 6, There is no folder 14. (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Medical Handbook, undated (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Medical Notebook, undated (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - "New Jersey Book" (land surveys and leases), 1792-1798 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Rental Account Book, 1793-1806 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Rental Account Book, 1794, 1797, 1799, 1801, 1803, 1807 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Rental arrears, 1808 January 1 (Box 47, Folder 20)
- Wilson, William H.
  - Account Book, 1868 June 1-September 30 (Box 48)
Adams, John Quincy.Letters from the Hon. John Quincy Adams to Edward Livingston. Hartford: Connecticut Anti-Masonic Tract Society, 1834.
Bard, Samuel.A Guide for Young Shepherds; or Facts and Observations on the Character and Value of Merino Sheep. New York: Collins and Co., 1811.
Livingston, Brockholst.Democracy: An Epic Poem by Aquiling Nimble-Chops, democrat. Canto first. New York: privately printed, 1794.
Livingston, Brockholst.A Faithful Picture of the Political Situation in New Orleans. Repr. ed. Boston: n.p., 1808.
Livingston, Brockholst.An Answer to Mr. Jefferson's Justification of his Conduct in the Case of the New Orleans Batture. Philadelphia: W. Fry, 1813.
Livingston, Brockholst.Letter from Edward Livingston to Roberts Vaux Regarding Advantages of Pennsylvania Prison System. Philadelphia: Joseph Harding, 1828.
Livingston, Brockholst.Rapport sur le project d'un Code penal Fait a l'Assemblée générale de l'état de la Louisiana. Paris: Antoine-Augustine Renouard, 1825.
Livingston, Brockholst.System of Penal Law, prepared for the State of Louisiana. New Orleans: Benjamin Levy, 1824.
Livingston, John (n.d.).Catalogue of law books, comprising a catalogue of a select law library, including the dates and prices of the latest editions of the most approved works ... Prepared by John Livingston. New York: Law Register, 1856.
Livingston, John.Livingston's Law Register. New York: Monthly Law Magazine, 1851.
Livingston, John Henry. Two sermons, delivered before the New-York missionary society; first on April 23d, in the Scots Presbyterian church, by the Rev. Dr. Livingston, The second on April 24th, in the North Dutch church, by the Rev. Dr. M’Knight. New York: Isaac Collins, 1799.
Livingston, John Henry. The Psalms of David, with hymns and spiritual songs. Also, the Catechism, Confession of faith, and liturgy, of the Reformed church in the Netherlands. For the use of the Reformed Dutch church in North America.. New York: G. Forman, 1796.
Livingston, Maturin.The Trial of the Hon. Maturin Livingston Against James Cheetham, for a Libel... New York: S. Gould, 1807.
Livingston, Philip.The Other Side of the Question, or, a Defense of the Liberties of North America. New York: James Rivington, 1774.
Livingston, Robert R.Essay on Sheep. New York: T. and J. Swords, 1809.
Livingston, Robert R.Essay on Sheep. Concord, New Hampshire: D. Coolidge, 1813.
Livingston, Robert R.Oration Delivered Before the Society of the Cincinnati of the State of New York. New York: Francis Childs, 1787.
Livingston, William.Eulogy on Rev. Aaron Burr. Boston: Green and Russell, 1758.
Livingston, William.A Letter to the... Lord Bishop of Landoff. New York: privately printed, 1768.
Livingston, William.A Review of the Military Operations in North America. London: R. and J. Dodsley, 1757.
Livingston, William.Collection of Tracts from the late Newspapers [The American Whig]. 2 vols. [1768-1769]
Livingston, William. The Independent Reflector [1754].
Sacandago Turnpike and Bridge Co. Minute Book, 1814-1819. Schenectady, New York. Manuscripts Division, Miscellaneous Bound
Skinner, Henry P. Journals, January 1, 1817-December 31, 1824. [Diary and Account Books] 4 vols. Hudson, New York. Manuscripts Division, Miscellaneous Bound
Agricultural association of Dutchess & Columbia. The Farmers' club of the counties of Dutchess and Columbia, wishing anxiously to promote a spirit of industry and improvement in agriculture, offer the following premiums for the year 1818. Removed to: Broadsides. Agricultural association.
The agricultural society of Columbia county, offer the following premiums for the year 1821. Removed to: Broadsides. Agricultural society.
Encouragement to farmers, their wives, daughters, and others... the Farmer's club of Dutchess and Columbia offer the following premiums for the year 1819. Removed to: Broadsides. Agricultural association.
Constitution and rules of the Agricultural society of Columbia county. Removed to: Broadsides. Agricultural society.
Notice to farmers. A meeting of the board of managers of the Agricultural society of the county of Columbia, was held at the house of William B. Flagler, in the city of Hudson, on Saturday, the 20th inst. [1833]. Removed to: Broadsides. Agricultural society.
Clermont society for the detection of horse thieves. Clermont, NY...February, 1869. Removed to: Broadsides. Clermont Society for the detection
The lion! And it came to pass in the days of Scott and Pierce, when all parties were at enmity, that John J. Lyon was nominated and elected as Clerk of Ontario county. [185-]. Removed to: Broadsides. The lion!
Saunders, John Auction of wood & timber. The subscribers will dispose at public sale,...the homestead farm of the late Walter T. Livingston. 1842. Removed to: Broadsides. Saunders, John
Jay, John By His Excellency John Jay, esquire, governor of the state of New-York. A proclamation. [Warning residents of Livinston that if further riots occur militia will be sent to quell them and the participants will be punished, 1798]. Removed to: Broadsides. New York (State) Governor, 1795-1801 (John Jay)
Know all men by these presents....[Promissory notes re money owed by or to Cornelius Low]. 1774. Removed to: Broadsides. Know all men by these presents.
U.S. Constitution. We the people of the United States.... [Poughkeepsie: Nicholas Power, 1788] Robert R. Livingston's copy, with marginal notes. Removed to: Book Division. F 1788 Un
A map of four farms lying near Johnstown in the Manor of Livingston, County of Columbia. Survey'd by direction of William Wilson esquire. March 1801 by Alex Thompson. Scale: 1 inch to 10 chains. 18 7/8 x 15 inches. Removed to: Map Division. Brun Guide 365.
A map of Great Lot No. 2 in the Hardenbergh Patent. [By:] Corn[eliu]s Tappen. Scale: 1 inch to 2 miles. 11 3/4 x 18 1/2 inches. Removed to: Map Division. Brun Guide 366.
A map [of] Lot No. 4 in the [Ha]rdenbergh Patent. Scale: 1 inch to 100 chains. 7 3/4 x 33 inches. Removed to: Map Division. Brun Guide 367.
A map of Lot No. 4 in the Hardenbergh Patent. Surveyed and run into lots AD 1788 at the request of John R. Livingston esq. [by:] James Cockburn. Scale: 1 inch to 100 chains. 7 3/8 x 39 inches. Removed to: Map Division. Brun Guide 368.
A map of Lot No. 1 in the Hardenbergh Pate[nt.] Scale: 1 inch to 100 chains. 10 1/4 x 32 5/8 inches. Removed to: Map Division. Brun Guide 369.
A map of Lot No. 24 in North East Town containing 911 acres as surveyed in 1794 [by:] Alex[ande]r. Thompson. Scale: 1 inch to 10 chains. 19 1/8 x 8 1/2 inches. Removed to: Map Division. Brun Guide 370.
Map of the northerly section of sub. div. Lot. No. 1 of the 24th allotment of the Kayaderoseras Patent. Henry Ramsay surveyor. Scale: 1 inch to 20 chains. 15 1/2 x 10 1/2 inches. Removed to: Map Division. Small [18--]Brun Guide 376.
Map of the Second Nine Partners Tract in Dutches [!] County, protracted by a scale of one hundred chains to an inch, as divided pursuant to the acts of the Assembly. - [c.1790] 13 1/2 x 8 inches. Removed to: Map Division. Brun Guide 378.
A map or draft of a ceartain tract and parcell of arable and low land of Collo. Henry Beekman being situate & lying within the limitts and bounds of the township of Rochester in the County of Ulster and Province of New York on the north & west side of said town on a ceartain place called by the Indians Nassosincks. on bouth sides of a ceartain creek that waters weg eg [!] Reinock or Menissincks. according and inpursuance [!] to his Indian purcheese and deed of conveyence from the trustees of Rochester, and is contned with the creek and flatts about thirteen hundred and thirty acres of low land from where the southwest bounds of the pattant of Rochester strikes the said creek to the bounds of the land belonging to the Kigstjeprew Indians. Performed the same the tenth day of October Anno Domini 1751 by me Jacob Hoornbeck. Scale: 1 inch to 20 chains. 40 1/2 x 14 3/4 inches. Removed to: Map Division. Brun Guide 379.
[Map. Post road & Kaskutahook. Surveyed 1765]. Scale: 1 inch to 660 feet. 15 5/8 x 24 3/4 inches; with extension on verso: 9 x 15 5/8 inches. Removed to: Map Division. Brun Guide 380.
A map shewing a number of the farms that are divided by the division line between lots no 1 & 2. surveyed in December 1803 by John Wigram. Scale: 1 inch to 10 chains. 8 x 106 inches. Removed to: Map Division. Brun Guide 381.
Subdivision of Lot No. 12 in the Good Beerkill Tract. Performed this 4th. day of Octr. 1797. Pr. Isaac Le Fever. Scale: 1 inch to 10 chains. 15 3/8 x 20 1/2 inches. Removed to: Map Division. Brun Guide 445.
Surveyed April 1, 1796 the tract returned to John Stevens esqr. and the lot of John Logans mostly included in the same the 6th. course which in the copy of the records is N. 74? 15' E. should be 74? West protracted from a scale of 10. ch[ains] to an inch the brook was not traversed [Signed:] Silas Condict. 31 1/2 x 12 3/4 inches. Removed to: Map Division. Brun Guide 448.
Partial Subject Index
Accounts receivable
40:1-3, 5
46:11, 14, 15, 18
47:1, 7, 9, 21
Adams, John Quincy, 1767-1848
30:5
Agricultural exhibitions--New York (State)
41:6-8
Agricultural laws and legislation--New York (State)
24:78, 79
Agricultural machinery
1:6
3:45
18:30
Agricultural Society of Dutchess and Columbia Counties
20:2, 5, 8, 9, 12, 50
21:18, 29, 30
22:3, 6, 70
23:14, 17, 41, 57, 61
24:31, 95, 98, 102
25:5, 32, 45, 46, 74
27:17, 57, 58
30:31
41:3-11
Agriculture--New York (State)
2:12
3:48
6:82
8:1, 2
12:7, 8
15:49
16:59, 71
17:43
20:46, 47
23:23, 64, 65
24:85, 91
25:94
26:56, 57, 58, 65, 92
27:8, 38
29:45
36:9
47:2
Apprentices--New York (State)
19:32
35:6, 8
Arrest--New York (State)
41:17
Baltimore (Md.)--Description and travel
33:45
Banking law--New York (State)
33:78
Bankruptcy
43:34
Banks and banking --New York (State)
41:3
46:12, 13
47:3, 4
Bank of Catskill
Bank of Columbia
Bank of Hudson 34:55, 56
Hudson River Bank 34:55, 56
44:14
Manhattan Bank-Poughkeepsie Branch 11:29, 78
Middle District Bank 20:87, 88
Bank of Plattsburgh 7:64; 28:82; 30:63
Barbary States
12:94
Bonaparte, Jerome, b. 1805
13:34
Books
3:85
8:33
9:64
14:39
19:70
20:23
Bridges--New York (State)
5:1
21:5
23:68
26:3
Burr, Aaron, 1756-1836
12:89
13:6, 9
15:20
Cholera
34:58, 59
37:76
Churches
9:70
12:38
15:46
18:60
27:35
36:60
37:18, 20, 21, 23, 27, 39, 45
38:8, 41
41:15
Clermont (N.Y.)
17:61
41:16, 19, 21
Clermont Academy
41:18
Clinton, Dewitt, 1769-1828
9:94
15:20
16:73
17:33, 36
29:22
32:37
Clover
3:42
18:23
21:32
22:12, 18
26:70
27:42, 56
32:35, 38, 40, 41
College of Physicians and Surgeons of the State of New York
15:68
Columbia County (N.Y.)
7:33, 36
11:18
13:69, 70, 71
25:15
Columbia County Medical Society
14:87
Coney Island (N.Y.)
32:61
Confiscations
43:36
Constables--New York (State)
6:41, 42
41:19
Coroners
11:83
Cuba--History
30:54, 83
Deeds--New York (State)
35:62
41:24
Depositions
43:39
Digitalis
1:50
Diseases
5:34
9:58
10:5, 46
12:64
13:27
14:47
18:6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 18, 50, 55
19:15, 21,
25
20:78, 89
21:36
25:43
26:68
27:12, 40
38:22
Distribution Bill, 1837
35:66
Draft
38:3
Dutchess and Columbia County Medical Society
2:60
Dutchess County (N.Y.)
15:26
Education
10:55
11:40
16:39, 41, 84, 86
18:2, 65
19:8, 14
See also schools
Ejectment--New York (State)
43:40
Election law
29:6, 20
Elections--New York (State)
1:45, 67, 69, 75, 78, 79
2:1, 3, 7, 10, 13, 31, 32, 41, 43, 48, 50, 52, 54, 55, 77, 78
3:54
4:50, 54, 55, 60, 61, 69, 71, 85
6:6, 41, 50, 53, 54, 76, 84
7:48, 77
8:4, 76
11:66, 71
13:7, 14, 17, 18, 20, 21
14:1, 68, 69
15:23
16:5
17:32
19:11
21:7, 47
24:104
25:97
26:93, 99
28:23, 23a, 24, 25
30:38, 39
41:25, 26, 27, 28
Embargo, 1807-1809
15:43, 73, 76
16:4
Embargo, 1812
18:68, 72
19:35
Europe--Politics and government
8:71
26:34
28:50
Flour-mills
3:22
4:13, 41, 90
5:33
9:19, 61
10:3
France--Description and travel
10:9, 19, 28, 58, 64
11:15
12:92
30:84
France--History--Revolution, 1789-1799
3:2, 20, 71
7:59, 63, 67
Freemasons
8:88
16:11
24:64
Fulton, Robert, 1765-1815
20:19
Fur trade
1:2
Genealogy
See under names of individual families
Glenn family
42:11
Grass
27:43
Great Britain--Politics and government
13:23
14:30
Guardian and ward
8:36
Hamilton, Alexander, 1757-1804
2:77
13:40
Hardenburgh Patent (N.Y.)
7:11
8:16
10:58
11:24, 33, 51, 63
13:77
15:27
18:15
23:40
25:56, 58, 59, 60, 64, 67
28:52
31:71, 72
Hardware
15:51
Highland Turnpike Co.
10:4, 38
15:24
16:20
17:22
18:12
19:69
23:45
29:21
31:60
34:51, 54
41:3
43:1, 2
House construction
8:87
16:60
32:22
33:48, 52, 54, 61
34:41, 42
Hudson River Railroad
38:6
41:15
Illegitimacy
43:44
Indentured servants--New York (State)
2:16, 44
23:28
Iron-founding
5:14, 17, 35, 49
Jackson, Andrew, 1767-1845
24:68
30:74
32: 69, 74
33:1
Jay's treaty, 1794
2:32
3:2, 5
Jefferson,Thomas, 1743-1826
7:7
11:53
14:60
Judges--New York (State)
1:45
28:36
33:72
Kossuth, Madame
38:26
Lafayette, Marie Joseph, Marquis de, 1757-1834
29:58
Land grants--New York (State)
43:4
Landlord and tenant--New York (State)
1:19, 34, 61
2:25, 77
3:38, 39, 40, 79, 93, 96
4:6, 34, 35, 40, 85
5:7, 16, 21, 22,, 26, 35, 42, 46, 55
6:3, 17, 48, 75, 89, 92, 94
7:18, 22, 45, 84
8:31
9:20
12:101
13:26
15:37, 73
41:1,2
Law--Cases
46:16, 17
Law--Study and teaching
9:52, 83, 88, 94, 100, 106
10:6, 42, 82
16:28, 87
19:50
Lawsuits
See Law--Cases
Lawyers--Licenses
20:78, 79
21:86
24:35, 89
Leases--New York (State)